The long-sought-after
barhopping!
Today is my first visit to Akabane.
I'm in Akabane for the first time!
Hatsuhane?
But I've heard a lot about Hashigo-zake and the image of Akabane, so
I'm really looking forward to it!
And it's only noon.
I can't believe we can drink in the afternoon.
I'm sorry, people of the world.
I only have a limited amount of time today.
I'm going to drink as much as I can.
As much as I can.
I love alleys like this
Lanterns are the best!
Oysters look delicious!
Lanterns are great!
If you're having dinner at home today
Please watch this video and feel like you're having a drink with me!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, wow!
Here we are.
I want to go to Carefree!
the best daytime drinking!
I'll come in
Please come in
Thank you very much.
Yay, yay!
So, first stop.
We'll start with beer.
Maybe a bottle of beer.
A medium beer bottle.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
I'm not very good at pouring.
How's that?
I'm terrible at it, right?
Have a good day, everyone.
Cheers.
I thought I was going to get a beer commercial.
My dream is to get a beer commercial.
I'm hungry.
Liver.
The head.
Gingko skewer
Myoga Cucumber
Seriously, a bottle of beer is delicious!
Sashimi looks delicious, too.
Oh, gingko nuts!
I love gingko nuts!
I'll keep this one.
I love ginkgo nuts!
I told you why I like them.
I like it because it's in my chawanmushi.
Myoga Cucumber
I love myoga.
My mom used to make miso soup with myoga
I love gingko!
Gingko is delicious.
Kiara eating a ginkgo nut
Chiara ate a ginkgo nut.
What?
What's this?
It's Saranth's favorite.
I have a feeling that Sarrance likes it.
I have a feeling that Sullins likes it.
What?
Stinky, stinky, stinky.
It hurts.
Ouch.
I'm scared.
But it hurts
Maybe I can't do it for a minute
I could do it with a gingko
It's good!
I'll eat up to 3 members per house
That's right!
That's great!
Oh, no.
So, what's next?
I'll do it when the test comes.
Ta-da!
Stuffed peppers.
I don't know who I'm talking about.
You know someone who would eat stuffed peppers?
Yes, I do.
Hana-chan.
Looks like she'd eat it.
So this is Hana-chan?
This is Hana-chan.
A little official Hana-chan.
Look at this!
These beautiful peppers, these shiny peppers...
This center-cooked green pepper is delicious!
Itadakimasu!
Yo, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, piano!
Yum!
Delicious!
The bitterness of the peppers and the sweetness of this meat really match each other and it's so delicious!
Ana, when you do a food report, you look at people with your eyes like this, like this.
And eat!
I've never heard of anyone being able to see it like that.
I don't know.
It's a gift.
I think it's a talent.
I've heard that good mimics are good singers.
What's so good about it?
It's delicious at the end.
It's delicious.
Smells good.
Is that a hand towel?
Sometimes a hand towel smells so good.
It must be.
It's Atas.
Atas?
Yes, that's right.
Atas.
It's my smell.
I smell like me.
Yes, I smell good.
I see.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're drinking like sake.
I want some sake, too.
I also want to drink a highball.
I'll have a highball next time.
I'll have a highball!
I haven't had a highball in a long time!
I love highballs!
Highballs are so good!
What about you, Mr. Yoshizaka?
Why don't you have a highball?
I'll have a highball.
Pee...
I'll have a Pee...
Pee.
Wait, that looks really heavy.
Oh no, beautiful women
100 beautiful women 120 beautiful women
Leaky channel
Bon appétit!
I don't need teeth!
Here it is!
My tooth standard
It's usually based on my teeth.
I'm going to report on the food.
I really don't need teeth.
Hitomi Takamatsu
There she is!
Bon appétit!
Mmm?
It's delicious.
Not too much? It's a little bit like it, isn't it?
If you look to the left and right, it looks a lot like it.
It's delicious.
Wait, it's delicious.
I know what you mean.
I can tell.
This is...
Jaga Butter
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na...
Oh, man.
I love this!
Oh, no, no, no!
I can smell the salted fish!
Jaga Butter with salted fish!
It will be 37 minutes soon!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
It's like a birthday!
Let's make it 37 minutes and 37 seconds.
How do you know when it's 37 minutes and 37 seconds?
I don't know.
Thirty-seven minutes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yes!
And I dropped my chopsticks in the worst 37 minutes.
I dropped my chopsticks.
Hell became 37 minutes on March 7!
I am happy to spend this time again this year with all of you whom I love so much!
Thank you very much!
I'm almost to 37 seconds.
It's here, it's here, it's here!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I know you guys think this is funny.
I'd like to do a question-and-answer session.
I've just sent out a message on social networking sites like Instagram.
I'd like to answer them at the next store.
Okay, let's go to the next store.
I'm sure it's nice to have a lolly that you got yourself.
Let's go to the second restaurant!
Great!
Wait. Wait.
This is the best kind of restaurant, but I wonder if they can see us.
Oh my God!
This is the best!
Here we are at the second restaurant.
Here we are at Dion!
I'd like to start with a lemon sour.
May I?
Lemon Sour with food?
Um... Motsuni-nikomi.
Senmaisashi.
Tako-Kimchi.
Yes, sir.
Tako-Kimuchi
Yes, please.
Ham and pork cutlet is good, isn't it?
I'll have the second lemon sour.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
I'll have some kimchi. It's a good one for the second dinner.
I know Mirian. Mirian on YouTube.
Then make this face.
Taku kimchi! Looks so good!
Bon appétit!
Do you see this?
I see it.
I think I can get the best features.
I watch a lot of Milian's YouTube.
A thousand stabbings.
Ta-da! A thousand stabbings!
Oh, shit!
I'm so sorry!
I love stewed pork!
Looks so delicious!
We have to do a Q&A about that!
We're getting a lot of questions.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to answer your questions.
I've received so many, so many, so many questions.
I'm going to answer them.
Okay, I'll answer quickly.
What do you do when you are tired?
Sauna.
I'd like to know how you tackle things you don't like, like baths and assignments, right away.
I think so too!
I don't do that at all.
I don't do it at all.
It's all about meeting deadlines.
I love taking a bath, so I rarely don't take a bath.
Why don't you put your favorite bath salts in it?
What would you like to do at a live performance?
But now that you've done the Jump Up tour, what would you like to do at the show?
I guess so.
I think it's the break time at Iyori's Cave of Iyori by Tesho Coorsion...
I've been saying that my whole life.
I'd love to do a live performance someday.
There are days when I'm so tired I can't move.
Do you have those days, Sauna?
If so, what do you do?
If you're physically and mentally exhausted, then your body is screaming for a break.
I think you should take a day off.
I ask myself the same question.
I think you should ask yourself if you can get through today.
I think it's better to ask yourself if you can get through today, and then move on to work.
If you work too hard, you'll break down one day.
I also have days when I don't work too hard.
I think it's best to have a day when you don't work so hard.
I'm impressed that you've been working so hard all this time.
Thank you.
There are days when I don't work hard, too.
What's your favorite e-collaboration song?
This one... it's impossible.
I can't pick one.
There are so many.
Songs that are fun to sing.
Songs that are fun to listen to
Songs that are fun to dance to.
There are too many to choose from, too many songs I like the intros to choose from
Subliminal for Youth?
Maybe it's a classic, but...
It makes me cry.
I especially like the second verse.
Shoko...
I feel like I can finally stand on the staff.
always makes me cry.
especially when we play it in a big venue.
Especially when we play at a big venue.
What is a true friend?
That's deep.
I don't have any friends.
I'm probably one of the five bows.
They're not like friends... or family.
They're special.
Friends?
But yeah.
You don't have to have any.
You only need people you really feel comfortable with.
Someone I can be myself with, and expose myself to.
I'm someone I can be comfortable with.
If it's too much for you, then...
That's not a true friend.
Someone you can expose yourself to will come along someday.
Even if the number of people is very small.
I have very few.
And I can't be asked about my singing.
How can I sing?
People often tell me I'm a good singer.
I'm really grateful for that.
I love singing because...
I had a friend who was a very good singer.
I had a friend who was really good.
I was pretty good at mimicking and capturing people's features, so I thought I would try to imitate her.
So I tried to imitate her.
That's how I came up with my originality.
That's how I came up with my original style.
I'm often asked
How can I become a better singer?
I appreciate the question.
I think you should start from mimicry.
I like MISIA and other singers a lot.
I like MISIA a lot, so I start by imitating her at karaoke.
and then gradually make it your own originality.
I'm worried about job hunting.
I'm trying to find a job.
I'm not job hunting because I joined the collaboration.
But I've been listening to my friends' stories.
If it's not going well, it's like they're denying themselves.
There are times when you wonder why.
I think that's when our idols come in.
You can listen to our songs or talk with us online.
You can talk to us online, or meet us in person, or come to our live shows.
You can listen to our songs, talk with us online, meet us in person, or come to our live shows.
I hope that we can give you the energy to work hard.
So please make use of us a lot.
Please do your best!
How to raise your self-esteem
Self-affirmation is
I'm really good at what I do.
I'm very negative in my appearance.
But don't think of it as negativity.
I try to be positive in my life.
The best way is not to say negative things.
There is such a thing as the spirit of speech.
Even if it's a lie.
That's what Ammika said.
It's not my technique.
Before going to bed...
"I was happy again today.
I heard it's good to say it out loud and go to sleep.
Then your brain will think it's a lie.
Even if it's a lie.
It's better to say it because your brain is listening.
But I'm always happy.
I always end up doing what I like.
I like taking a bath.
I take a bath with my favorite bath salts.
I go to bed thinking, "I'm so happy today.
No matter how hard the day is.
I'm happy today, no matter how hard the day is.
It might lead to the next step.
So please give it a try.
If you have a good day, please let me know.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you for everything!
Hamkatsu
Amkatsu
Excuse me.
Huh? What?
You're acting a little strange all of a sudden.
I don't like to eat in front of people.
What? Huh?
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
Yes.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm not eating.
I'm eating.
One more time.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit. - Bon appétit. - Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
Can I have a beer?
It's about my fourth or fifth beer.
But I'm still back, and it's reset.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I was serious.
I'm so happy.
I should just say I'm happy.
Say happy.
Don't say it.
Happy!
Happy.
How's it going?
My eyes are starting to get a little red.
Yes, they are.
Rice balls.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Backup time.
Then, can I ask you to tell me about your recent funny story?
A funny story?
It was 15 years ago.
Recently.
I was on the train.
And there was a woman sitting in front of me who looked like an educated mother.
There was a boy who was not even in elementary school, maybe the oldest in kindergarten, and he was sitting there.
His mother was an educational mom, so she was holding English cards.
He had fruit cards.
I showed him an apple card.
What's this?
Apple.
What's this one?
Grapes.
That's not a grape.
This is a grape.
I'm a very educated person.
At first, I didn't care about the people around me or anything.
She's a bit of an educated mom.
I was like...
I didn't mind.
But then, there are all kinds of cards.
This is banana
Grape
Apple
and this one is a peach card.
I got a card of peach.
I thought it would be called "Peach" because of the peach card.
So we were listening to her like this, and the moment the word "peach" came up
As soon as the "Peach" card came out, the girl said "Bermian" with a pronunciation that I have never heard before.
Bermian
Bermian Bermian Bermian Bermian Bermian Bermian Bermian Bermian
You have that too, don't you?
I really do.
Yamanote Line
Really Yamanote Line
I don't have it.
Your mother doesn't have it.
Why don't you do it and make your mother laugh again?
So what's going?
What's going?
It's peach.
Peach.
You look like one of those people who's already been on it.
Winner!
Hey, Noogi, have some wasabi powder...
Oh, yes!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's good.
What is it?
What?
It's delicious.
I don't know.
How do you eat it, Yori?
When the camera's not rolling.
He says, "It's on the picture.
Eat this, Yori.
It's delicious!
Yori is sweeter when she's off camera.
Maybe that's good... on the contrary...
I'm drinking corn chahai now!
I'm having a corn chahai to finish it off...
That's all for now!
If this video is very popular, I think I'll make it a series.
Please let me know your favorite places to go drinking!
Thank you all for your hard work today!
That's it!
Bye bye!
A little tipsy
The end